{
    "subject": "Kelly_Cramer",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Kevin_Buchanan",
    "human_readable": "Kelly Cramer is married to Kevin Buchanan.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9576665163040161,
            "question": "Name the person who is married to Kelly Cramer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9380565285682678,
            "question": "If Kevin Buchanan's wife is Kelly Cramer, what can you say about their relationship status?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9134001731872559,
            "question": "Who is Kelly Cramer married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8725044131278992,
            "question": "Is Kevin Buchanan married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8360207676887512,
            "question": "What type of relationship exists between Kelly Cramer and Kevin Buchanan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7847134470939636,
            "question": "Who is Kelly Cramer's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6491879224777222,
            "question": "To whom is Kelly Cramer connected?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6448843479156494,
            "question": "What is the name of Kevin Buchanan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10619509220123291,
            "question": "Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship according to the statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04049599915742874,
            "question": "Identify the individuals mentioned in a spousal relationship within the given statement."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Kelly Cramer is married to Kevin Buchanan.",
            "html": "yago_30818_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the individuals involved in a marital relationship according to the statement?",
            "html": "yago_30818_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Kevin Buchanan's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_30818_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom is Kelly Cramer connected?",
            "html": "yago_30818_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_30818_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention multiple instances where Kelly Cramer and Kevin Buchanan are described as being in relationships with each other. For example, the document states, \"Although Kelly and Joey married, Kelly couldn't fight her feelings for Kevin and ended their marriage to engage in a relationship with Kevin.\" This clearly indicates that they were indeed married at some point."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}